Sheet Music Collection
Sheet Music Collection
- Sheet music
  - Lesser-known composers
    - Loughborough, Raymond How Lovely is the Hand of God, poem by Dorothy Dickinson, vocal (song) (medium voice) (Oversize 9)
    - Lowthian, Caroline Myosotis Waltzes for the PianoForte, piano (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Ludebuehl, J. P. O Jesu We Adore Thee, verse by A. T. Russell, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 9)
    - Luders, Gustav Heidelberg (Stein Song) from The Prince of Pilsen, lyrics by Frank Pixley, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Luders, Gustav The Message of the Violet from The Prince of Pilsen, lyrics by Frank Pixley, vocal (song) (Oversize 9)
    - Luders, Gustav Selection from the Musical Fantasy "Woodland", arr. by Hilding Anderson (orchestral sheet music) (handwritten cue sheet) (Oversize 9)
    - Ludovic, G. Song of Marguerite (Op. 33), keyboard (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - Lugghesi, F. The Moonbeams are Glancing, words by H. B. I., piano (solo) (signed by E. L. Riddell) (Oversize 9)
    - Lutz, Meyer Skirt Dance as Danced in the Burlesque "Faust up to Date", piano (solo) (Oversize 9)
    - MacDermid, James G. For the Mountains Shall Depart, vocal (song) two copies (Oversize 10)
    - Macdougall, H. C. Jesus Lover of My Soul (high voice), vocal (song) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 10)
    - MacDowell, Edward Sechs Gedichte nach Heinrich Heine: No. 2 in F min (Scotch) (Op. 31), keyboard (solo) (Oversize 10)
    - MacDowell, E. A. Drei Poesien für Pianoforte zu vier Händen (Op. 20), piano (four hands) (Oversize 10)
    - MacDowell, E. A. Suite für grosses Orchester für Pianoforte zu 4 Händen (Op. 42), piano (four hands) (Oversize 10)
    - Mack, Albert A. The Song of the Shulamite (Song of Solomon Chapter II, verses 8-17) (Op. 17), vocal (song for soprano with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 10)
    - Mack, E. Cinderella Waltz, keyboard (solo) (signed by Alice M. Corkle) (Oversize 10)
    - Mack, E. The Golden Chain: a Collection of Gems for the piano forte: My Pa's Waltz, piano (solo) (Oversize 10)
    - Maker, Fred C. Arise, Shine, vocal (song, with organ accompaniment) (Oversize 10)
    - Malotte, Albert Hay The Lord's Prayer, vocal (song) (signed by Frank Love) (Oversize 10)
    - Mana-Zucca Love's Pilgrimage, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 10)
    - Marenco Grand Selection from Ballet "Excelsior", (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 10)
    - Marks, Eugene F. I Would Love Thee, vocal (duet) (soprano and contralto) (Oversize 10)
    - Marryvale, Frank Sleigh Bells / Polka-Galop, piano (solo with bells) (Oversize 10)
    - Marston, G. W. My God and Father, While I Stray, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Martin, Easthope The Mountebanks: Song Cycle for Four Voices, lyrics by Helen Taylor, vocal (song cycle) (Oversize 10)
    - Martin, Easthope Come to the Fair, from the album Three More Songs of the Fair; lyric by Helen Taylor, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Marzials, Theodore Twickengham Ferry, vocal (song) (signed by Jennie Leland Butler) (Oversize 10)
    - Marzials, Theodore A Summer Shower, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Marzo, Eduardo Jesus Lives (Op. 99), vocal (song with violin obligato) (high voice) (Oversize 10)
    - Marzo, Eduardo Sun of My Soul Thou Saviour Dear, verse by J. Keble, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 10)
    - May, T. G. Juanita, arr. by Ross Hilton, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 10)
    - Mazas, F. 18 kleine Duette für 2 Violinen/18 petits Duos pour 2 Violons/18 short Duets for 2 Violins, revidirt und genau bezeichnet von Henri Petri, Heft I (Op. 38), violin (duets) (Oversize 10)
    - Meissler, Josef Dream Faces: Waltz on the Popular Song, piano (solo) (Oversize 10)
    - Meredith, I. H. The Shepherds' Vision, words by Grant Colfax Tullar, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (with violin obligato) two copies (Oversize 10)
    - Merz, Carl Deliciosa or Leonore Polka, piano (solo) (Oversize 10)
    - Messager, André Long Ago in Alcala, words by F. E. Weatherly & Adrian Ross with an additional verse by B. B., vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Meyer, George W. Hiawatha's Melody of Love, lyric by Alfred Bryan & Artie Mehlinger, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Maurice-Michell, F. Room in My Heart (There Is Room in My Heart for Thee), words by E. S. S. Elliot, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Millard, H. Under the Daisies, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Millöcker, C. The Beggar-Student Waltz, piano (solo) (Oversize 10)
    - Minetti, C. Song of Bethlehem: A Christmas Song, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 10)
    - Miniello, C. Vieni Fanciulla Mia – Notturno Sentimentale, mandolin (solo) (Oversize 10)
    - Moelling, T. Come Chase that Starting Tear Away, from Moore's National Airs, adapted to an appropriate melody, vocal (song) (signed by Phillie A Stover) (Oversize 10)
    - Molloy, J. L. Clang of the Wooden Shoon, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Monti, V. Les Valses à la Mode: Si J'Osais… valse lente, keyboard (solo) (signed by Jean Aldrich Conrad) (Oversize 10)
    - Moore, Hartley Dreaming Alone in the Twilight, words by Carl Clemson, vocal (duet with violin or ‘cello obbligato) (Oversize 10)
    - Moore, Raymond Sweet Marie, words by Cy Warman, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Morse, Woolson Vocal Gems from Dr. Syntax, words by J. Cheever Goodwin, vocal (songs) (Oversize 10)
    - Moses-Tobani, Theodore Puppenfee Pa-pa Ma-ma Waltz, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 10)
    - Moszkowski, Maurice Quatre Morceaux pour Violon et Piano (Op. 82, 1-2): Les Nymphes, Caprice, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 10)
    - Moszkowski, Maurice Quatre Morceaux pour Violon et Piano (Op. 82, 3-4): Mélodie, Humoresque, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 10)
    - Motzan, Otto Bright Eyes Fox Trot, also by M. K. Jerome, orchestration by Arthur Lange (orchestral sheet music) (optional vocal line) (Oversize 10)
    - Moul, Alfred St. Kilda Valse, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 10)
    - Murdock, Mackenzie Hame o' Mine, vocal (song) (Oversize 10)
    - Murnagh, James J. You Are My Bluebird, also by Rosario Pellegrino (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 10)
    - Neidlinger, W. H. The Undimmed Star of Bethlehem, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 10)
    - Neidlinger, W. H. Boat Song, vocal (song) (soprano) (Oversize 10)
    - Neidlinger, W. H. Oh, That We Two Were Maying, (vocal duet) (soprano and baritone) (Oversize 10)
    - Neidlinger, W. H. Spirit of God, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 10)
    - Neidlinger, W. H. The Village Blacksmith, poem by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow, vocal (choral) (Oversize 10)
    - Neruda, Franz Berceuse slave d'après un chant polonaise pour violon avec accompagnement de Piano (Op. 11), violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 10)
    - Nevin, Ethelbert Narcissus (Op. 13), piano (solo) (Oversize 10)
    - Nevin, Ethelbert One Spring Morning (Frühlingsmorgen), vocal (song) (soprano) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 10)
    - Nevin, George B. At the Cross, vocal (song) two copies (Oversize 10)
    - Nevin, George B. My Bonnie Lass She Smile, vocal (choral) two copies, one signed "Beal," one signed "Myers" (Oversize 10)
    - Nevin, George B. Ring on Sweet Bells, vocal (duet) (tenor and baritone) two copies (Oversize 10)
    - Nevin, George B. The Songs my Sainted Mother Sang, words by Eva Martindale vocal (solo and chorus) (men's voices) (Oversize 10)
    - Nevin, George B. My Shepherd, vocal (choral) (in envelope signed by Winifred Myers) (Oversize 10)
    - Nicodé, Jean Louis Walzer-Kapricien (Op. 10), piano (four hands) (Oversize 11)
    - Nicodé, Jean Louis Bilder aus dem Süden: Heft I (Op. 29), piano (four hands) (Oversize 11)
    - Nicodé, Jean Louis Bilder aus dem Süden: Heft II (Op. 29), piano (four hands) (Oversize 11)
    - Jean Louis Nicodé Bilder aus dem Süden: Heft III (Op. 29), piano (four hands) (Oversize 11)
    - Nicodé, Jean Louis Eine Ballscene Walzer für das Pianoforte zu vier Händen (Op. 26), componirt und Herrn Louis Stettheimer in Freudschaftzugeeignet, piano (four hands) (Oversize 11)
    - Nicolai, J. Overtüre zu "Lustige Weiber", piano (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Norton, Mrs. Love Not!, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Norton, Mrs. Outward Bound, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Novello, Ivor Keep the Home-Fires Burning (‘Till the Boys Come Home), words by Lena Guilbert Ford, vocal (song) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 11)
    - Oberndorfer, Marx E. Three Prison Sonnets, words by Ralph Chaplin, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Oesten, Theodore Reminiscences d'Operas, Collection de Fantaisies Elegantes en forme de potpourri sur des themes d'operas moderns et favoris: Donizetti: Lucia di Lammermoor, piano (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Oesten, Theodore Répertoire de l'opéra pour les jeunes pianists: Belisario (opera de Donizetti), piano (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - O'Hara, Geoffrey Over Yonder Where the Lilies Grow, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - O'Hara, Geoffrey The Living God, words by Gordon Johnstone, vocal (song) (medium voice) (Oversize 11)
    - O'Hara, Geoffrey I Love a Little Cottage, words by Roscoe Gilmore Stott, vocal (duet) (soprano and tenor) (Oversize 11)
    - Olcott, Chauncey Mother Machree, lyric by Rida Johnson Young, music also by Ernest R. Ball, vocal (duet) (contralto or baritone and soprano or tenor) (Oversize 11)
    - Openshaw, John Love Comes But Once, vocal (song) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 11)
    - Operti, G. Hush, my Darlings, do not Weep (song of the Famishing Irish Mother), words by John Keynton, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Panormo, F. The Bird Waltz for the Harp or Piano, (harp or piano solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Parker, Horatio W. Come, see the place where Jesus lay, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 11)
    - Parry, John Dost thou love me, Sister Ruth?, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 11)
    - Parsons, George T. I Heard the Voice of Jesus Say, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Paul, F. Transcriptions of Popular Songs: Rock of Ages, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Paull, E. T. Battle of the Nations: March Descriptive, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Paull, E. T. Charge of the Light Brigade March, keyboard (solo) two copies, one signed "Adsit" (Oversize 11)
    - Paull, E. T. Charge of the Light Brigade March, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Paull, E. T. The Circus Parade March-Twostep, piano (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Paull, E. T. The Home Coming March, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Paull, E. T. Silver Sleigh Bells: Novelette-Descriptive, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Paull, E. T. The Triumphant Banner, March Two-Step, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Paull, E. T. A Warmin' Up in Dixie, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Penn, Arthur A. Sing Along!, arr. by George W. Trinkaus, vocal (choral) (includes school and community lyrics) (Oversize 11)
    - Persley, George W. Slumber not Darling, words written by Arthur W. French, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Phillips, A. Fred I am always building Castles in the Air, words by Ted Garton, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Phillips, Louis Baker Lord, Thou Hast Been Our Dwelling Place, vocal (song) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 11)
    - Phillips, Theodore I wants a Ping Pong Man, March & Two-Step (intro: Ma Starlight Sue), banjo (solo) (Oversize 11)
    - Pike, Harry Hale Love of Jesus, All Divine, vocal (duet with organ accompaniment) (soprano and baritone) (Oversize 11)
    - Pinkney, H. Would I were with thee, poetry by the Honorable Mrs. Norton, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 11)
    - Pinsuti, Ciro Bedouin Love Song, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Pinsuti, Ciro Crusaders, poetry by William Duthie, vocal (choral) (Oversize 11)
    - Pinsuti, Ciro We'll Gaily Sing and Play, vocal (choral) (Oversize 11)
    - Pleyel, Ignace Six petits duos pour deux violins, recus et doigtés par Fr. Herman, violin (duet) (Oversize 11)
    - Porter, H. W. I Will Give You Rest, vocal (duet) (soprano and alto) (Oversize 11)
    - Pratt, Charles E. Lingard's Capt. Jinks of the Horse Marines, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Proch, H. Alpine Horn/The Horn of the Alps/Das Alpenhorn, vocal (song) (signed by Miss Jennie Butler) (Oversize 11)
    - Puerner, C. Chinese Patrol, (orchestral sheet music) (in folder with/shares page space with Egyptian March; by Ch. Puerner) (Oversize 11)
    - Pyke, C. M. Only a Leaf of Sweet Clover, written by George Cooper, vocal (song) (Oversize 11)
    - Rab, W. Wiener Humor: Walzer (Op. 31), (orchestral sheet music) (includes hand-written sheet music for piano part) (Oversize 11)
    - Raff, Joachim Dans la foret/Im Walde, piano (four hands) (signed T. M. Osborne) (Oversize 11)
    - Raff, Joachim 12 morceaux pour piano à quatre mains (Op. 82), piano (four hands) (Oversize 11)
    - Reinecke, Carl Compositionen von Carl Reinecke: Musik zu Hofmann's Kindermärch v. "Nussknacker u. Mausekönig" (Op. 46), piano (four hands) (Oversize 12)
    - Rice, Gitz You can't Drive my Dreams Away, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 12)
    - Rico, J. Les Valses Célèbres de J. Rico: La Seduzione: Valse Napolitaine, piano (solo) (Oversize 12)
    - Ritter, E. W. Petit Boléro, original music by H. Ravina (Op. 62), violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 12)
    - Roberts, Charles J. Funiculi-Funicula March and Two-Step, (orchestral sheet music) (includes hand-written sheet music parts) (folder says "Piano score missing") (Oversize 12)
    - Rockwell, George Noyes Calvary, vocal (duet) (soprano and tenor) (Oversize 12)
    - Roff, J. A. A Famous Railway Line! (Song & Chorus), vocal (song) ("Compliments of E. L. McIntire" written on cover) (Oversize 12)
    - Roger, Victor Vocal Gems from The Little Trooper, from the French of H. Raymond and A. Mars, adapted by Clay M. Greene, music also by William Furst, vocal (songs) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Roger, Victor Vocal Gems from The Little Trooper, as Produced by The Della Fox Opera Co., from the French of H. Raymond and A. Mars, adapted by Clay M. Greene, music also by William Furst, vocal (songs) (Oversize 12)
    - Rogers, James H. Great Peace have they which love Thy law, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Roma, Caro In the Garden of My Heart, also by Ernest R. Ball, arr. by W. C. O'Hare, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies with different ornamentation on covers, one signed "Myers," (Oversize 12)
    - Ronald, Landon Four Songs of the Hill: No. 2 (for Soprano or Tenor), words by Harold Simpson, vocal (songs with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 12)
    - Ross, Gertrude Art Songs of Japan/Yamata Shirabe, written upon Traditional Japanese Themes and Poems, vocal (songs with piano accompaniment) (low voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Russell, Kennedy Poor Man's Garden, words by Royden Barrie, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) two copies, both signed by Winifred Seely Myers (Oversize 12)
    - Ryder, T. P. Enchantment: Valse de Concert, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 12)
    - Rziha, Francis Irene Polka, as played by the Steyermarkische, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 12)
    - Rziha, Francis Evergreen Galop of the Steyermarkische, keyboard (solo) (marked "Miss Mary E. Morgan, with compliments of Senator Hall," "22nd July 1849") (Oversize 12)
    - Saar, Louis Victor Blessed be the Lord (Op. 92), vocal (duet) (soprano or tenor and alto or baritone) (Oversize 12)
    - Salter, Mary Turner O Lord of Life, vocal (song with piano or organ accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Sanderson, Wilfrid God Be With our Boys to-Night, words by Fred. G. Bowles, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 12)
    - Sanderson, Wilfrid Friend O'Mine, words by Fred. E. Weatherly, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 12)
    - Sanderson, Wilfrid Shipmates O'Mine, words by Edward Teschemacher, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (low voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Schertzinger, Victor L. Marcheta, arranged for mixed quartet by Daniel Doré, vocal (choral), Croxton Edition, two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Schertzinger, Victor L. Marcheta, arranged for mixed quartet by Daniel Doré, vocal (choral), Franklin Edition, two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Schertzinger, Victor L. Marchéta (A Love Song of Old Mexico), vocal (song) (Oversize 12)
    - Schmidt, Henry Sunset Waltz, piano (solo) (signed by Bettie A. Stover) (Oversize 12)
    - Schmidt, Henry The Hero's Quick Stop, dedicated to the New York Light Guard and Boston Light Infantry, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 12)
    - Schnecker, P. A. The Heralds of Heaven, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (includes violin obligato) (Oversize 12)
    - Schnecker, P. A. Immanuel, vocal (duet with piano or organ accompaniment) (soprano and alto) (Oversize 12)
    - Schwartz, Arthur Seven Song Hits from the American Musical Romance Virginia, lyrics by Albert Stillman, book by Laurence Stallings and Owen Davis, vocal (songs) (Oversize 12)
    - Schytte, Ludwig Standard compositions by European Composers for the Pianoforte: Ghosts/Les Spectres, edited and fingered by Maurits Leefson, piano (solo) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 12)
    - Scott, Cyril The Unforeseen (Op. 74), words by Rosamund Marriott Watson, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Seitz, Ernest The World is Waiting for the Sunrise, words by Eugene Lockhart, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (low voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Shelley, Harry Rowe Sacred Songs: The Resurrection, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (signed "Winifred S. Myers-Radnor") (Oversize 12)
    - Shelley, Harry Rowe Sacred Songs: Abide with me, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (medium voice) two copies, one signed by Winifred S. Myers (Oversize 12)
    - Sinding, Christian Suite für Pianoforte zu 4 Händen (Op. 35), piano (four hands) (Oversize 12)
    - Sitt, Hans Kleine Vortragsstücke für Violin emit begleitung des Pianoforte oder einer zweiten Violine in progressiver Schwierigkeit: No. 2, Wiegenlied (Lullaby, Berceuse) (Op. 73), violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 12)
    - Smith, Clay Sorter Miss You, arr. by George J. Trinkaus, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Smith, Emily Arizona March & Two-Step, arranged by E. T. Paull, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 12)
    - Smith, H. Wakefield O Haste for the Night is entrancing, Venetian Serenade, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and baritone) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Smith, Miss A Place in Thy Memory Dearest, words by the author of The Collegians, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (light signature of Phillie A. Stover) (Oversize 12)
    - Söderman, A. Peasant Wedding March, words by Julia Goddard, vocal (choral) two copies, one signed M. K. Robinson (Oversize 12)
    - Söderman, A. Peasants' Wedding March, English words by Charlotte H. Coursen, vocal (choral) (piano accompaniment for rehearsal only) (Oversize 12)
    - Speaks, Oley Choice Sacred Songs by Famous Composers: Thy Will Be Done, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Speaks, Oley Choice Sacred Songs by Famous Composers: Heaven is my Home, vocal (song) (low voice) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Speaks, Oley Saviour, Breathe an Evening Blessing, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Speaks, Oley Over the Hills and home Again: A Wayfarer's Song, words by Daniel S. Twohig, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Spier, Larry A Night of Love, words by B. G. de Sylva, arranged by Charles N. Grant, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Spindler, F. Fresh Life/Frisches Leben, keyboard (solo) (signed by Lois Secor; "Lansing Mich." written on cover) (Oversize 12)
    - Spross, Charles Gilbert Come Down, Laughing Streamlet, verse by Alfred H. Hyatt, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 12)
    - Spross, Charles Gilbert Choice Sacred Songs by Famous Composers: I do not ask O Lord, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Spross, Charles Gilbert Sacred Duets by the Best Modern Composers: The Lord is my shepherd, vocal (duet with organ or piano accompaniment) (soprano and baritone) (Oversize 12)
    - Spross, Charles Gilbert Minor and Major, verse by Minnie K. Breid, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 12)
    - Spross, Charles Gilbert Christmas Songs by Famous Composers: O Little Town of Bethlehem, vocal (song with piano accompaniment and violin obligato ad lib) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Spross, Charles Gilbert Choice Sacred Songs by Famous Composers: O Love That Wilt Not Let Me Go, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (low voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Spross, Charles Gilbert Choice Sacred Songs by Famous Composers: O Love That Wilt Not Let Me Go, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Spross, Charles Gilbert There's a Lark in My Heart, verse by James King Duffy, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed "W Myers") (high voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Squire, W. H. In an Old-fashioned Town, words by Ada Leonora Harris, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (low voice) (Oversize 12)
    - Stewart, Dorothy The Road of Used-to-be, words by Frederick H. Martens, vocal (song) (Oversize 12)
    - Stewart, H. J. Easter Songs by Famous Composers: He is Risen!, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Stewart, R. P. The Cruiskeen Lawn (Song of the Battle-Eve), poetry written by Thomas Moore, vocal (choral) (Oversize 12)
    - Stoughton, R. S. The Heart of God, words by Daniel S. Twohig, vocal (song) (Oversize 12)
    - Streabbog, L. Oiseaux de Paradis pour piano: No. 1, Valse Mignonne (Op. 78), piano (solo) (Oversize 12)
    - Stromberg, John Vocal and Instrumental Selections from Weber & Field's New Burlesque Production Twirly-Whirly: Come Down Ma Evenin' Star, lyrics by Edgar Smith and Robert B. Smith, music also by W. T. Francis, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by M. V. Conrad) (Oversize 12)
    - Taubert The Linden Tree, words by Cristabel, vocal (song) (soprano) (signed by Cora M. Dodson) (Oversize 12)
    - Taylor, Bianchi Will Thou Remember Me?, sung by Mr. Machin, written by Thomas Blake, Esq., vocal (song) (Oversize 12)
    - Taylor, Deems Part-Songs for Women's Voices: Wake Thee, Now, Dearest/Pridi Ty Šuhajko, Czecho-Slovak folksong, edited and arranged with English translation, vocal (choral) (female voices) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Taylor, Raymond A Signal from Mars March and Two Step, arranged by E. T. Paull, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 12)
    - Thaler, Rudolf Marching Through Georgia March & Two-Step, piano (solo) (Oversize 12)
    - Thomas, Ambroise Celebrated Arias, Duets, Trios, Quartets, and Quintets: Légères Hirondelles/"O lightly-flitting swallows," Duetto des Hirondelles from the opera Mignon, English version by Alma Strettell, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and baritone) two copies (Oversize 12)
    - Thomas, J. R. The Day When You'll Forget Me, words by Morgan, vocal (song) (Oversize 12)
    - Thompson, Lewis S. D. K. E. Waltz, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 12)
    - Tonassi, P. Collezione di Pot-pourris per chitarra sopra motivi d'opere di Donizetti, Pacini e Verdi composti da P. Tonassi: Secondo Pot-pourri sull Opera Lucia di Lammermoor di Donizetti, guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 12)
    - Topliff, R. Consider the Lillies, vocal (song) (Oversize 12)
    - Trinkaus, T. P. Keepsakes, original words and music by J. C. Macy, vocal (song with guitar accompaniment) (Oversize 12)